<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Database>
    <EnglishText>
        <!-- Antiquity -->
        <!-- Famine Crisis -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_FAMINE_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Antiquity Famine Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_FAMINE_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Food shortages strain your empire, hampering city growth.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A Drier Summer</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A farmer looks on at a field of dead crops. The rains were later and lighter this year. Those living in the great cities of the world's civilizations notice nothing, until food prices start to rise and migrants from neighboring nations appear on their doorstep. Where will these people go and how will they find food now?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Send the masses to the Towns</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Unlock the Empty Storage and Overworked Farmers crisis policies.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001C_NAME">
            <Text>Let them build shanty towns in the Cities</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001C_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Unlock the City Slum and City Migration crisis policies.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Shrinking Storehouses</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The hungry masses have begun to leave small towns for massive cities, but no relief can be found. The city warehouses are practically empty and what little food merchants are selling comes with a hefty price. Once bright eyes are now sullen and once full bellies are empty.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Hungry Masses</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A young child looks up at the cloudless sky. "Why have the rain gods forsaken us now?" they cry out. A stark contrast is seen across the land, the cities are exploding with people, while small towns are empty and silent. The wealthy have retreated to their castles while the poor bang on walls and wait in lines, clamoring for food.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Rainfall on the Horizon</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Never has rain felt so good. Children laugh in the streets, jumping in puddles, while parents smile on. Few survived this ordeal, and those who did look worse for wear. Yet, there is hope on the horizon. Perhaps the rural migrants and city folk can get along after all.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Antiquity is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
        <!-- Succession Crisis -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_SUCCESSION_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Antiquity Succession Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_SUCCESSION_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>The death of an heirless ruler causes a diplomatic disaster.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Royal Funeral</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A nation mourns the Emperor's death. But in the dark halls of the palace, court attendents have already begun to scheme. The Emperor died without naming an heir. Within the empire several factions begin to prepare a nominee, while our neighbors look on with interest hoping to take advantage of the chaos.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots. Unlock the Royal Banquet City Project. Diplomatic relations worsen.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A Demand Refused</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The power vacuum only grows each day without a ruler. Neighboring kings and queens are demanding their kids are named the true ruler of our great nation, but each one is refused. Even the greediest of court advisors knows that power is best kept within the nation where they will have more control over the next ruler. With a recent sighting of troops near the border, the search for an acceptable ruler grows more desperate.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Diplomatic relations worsen.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A Nation Divided</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Everyday townsfolk argue in the streets. Who is the legitimate ruler? The Emperor's brother has amassed an army in the North, while the Emperor's wife has gathered the support of the aristocrats in the capital. Both claim to be the true ruler, but our neighbors are refusing to recognize either one. We are divided and isolated.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Diplomatic relations worsen.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>The One True Ruler</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A sword pulled from a stone. A glowing figure in a lake. Almost by divine intervention the true heir has been found. The young man rallies the generals, the court attendants, and the aristocrats. The Emperor's brother and wife both have no choice but to acknowledge the legitimacy of our new ruler. Now that the empire's internal struggles have been resolved we can focus on rehabilitating our international image.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Antiquity is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
        <!-- Exploration -->
        <!-- Isolationism Crisis -->
         <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_ISOLATIONISM_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Exploration Isolationism Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_ISOLATIONISM_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Isolationist policy has gripped the nation, leading to harsh trade restrictions.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>The Rising Storm</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The great civilizations of the world have risen, and in their rise others, too, ascend. Once metalworking, agriculture, and the growth of cities were limited to points on the landscape; now, these are commonplace in all but the most remote corners of the world. Those once thought barbarians now lay equal claim to the mantle of civilization, and the learning of the city centers extends far beyond the boundaries of the known world. With this comes the question: Why are you ascendant, and we are not?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. New hostile independent powers are arriving.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Rumors and Portents</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>In the spaces between, in the distant points on the map, the steady growth of prosperity – and population – intensifies even as the great civilizations of the world expand. Land once thought wasteland turns to pasture, and expanding families mean more second and third children eager to make a name for themselves. Ambitions grow, and the eyes of the steppes and mountains, the forests and deserts turn hungrily towards the great cities.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Independent encampments grow stronger.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>The Scourge Unveiled</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Ambition finds a home in the hearts of the once-scattered people of the places in between – a great scourge has amassed with an eye towards the settled world. A scourge is not one strand, but many – each an army led by commanders seeking their own chance at dominion, seeking to claim the mantle of civilization… or leave it shattered. With their arrival comes a fracturing of what peace remains in the land. The time has come to kill or be killed, to fight or perish, to seek to catch the whirlwind in a net.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots. Independent encampments grow stronger.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A World Broken</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The scourge has ended, and the world yet turns. But its shape is unfamiliar. Peoples displaced from their homelands make new homes where they have settled. Forever gone is a world of a singular city and a vast barbarian hinterland; now, those that city-dwellers once looked down upon wear their own crowns, and tongues once thought unfit for the capital are spoken by monarchs. The ancient era has passed on to a new time of interconnection. Even we have not remained untouched, as a wave of refugees and immigrants reshape who we are, what tongue we speak, and what stories we tell.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Antiquity is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EDC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
        <!-- Inflation Crisis -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_INFLATION_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Exploration Inflation Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_INFLATION_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>An influx of treasure fleet gold leads to ever rising prices.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Rising Prices</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A lady scoffs at the latest market prices. Her weekly food costs have tripled in the last month alone. Similar grumbles can be heard around the city. If we just had more treasure fleets, every citizen could eat like a king!</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Unending Debts</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Royal advisors hide in their chambers as the Queen storms around the castle. How could our great nation be so deep in debt? Print more money! Demand more treasure tributes! She steadies her shaking hands and takes a breath. Perhaps we can take another loan to cover this one?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>You Can't Eat Gold</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The streets are littered with gold, but all anyone wants is a bite to eat. Wealth is meaningless when everyone has it. Is everyone now a King or a Peasant?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Stabilizing Prices</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Prices have begun to fall, and now hope begins to rise. The world is almost as it was before. The wealthy are wealthy and the poor are poor. Well, maybe some things need to change ...</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Exploration is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EIC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
    </EnglishText>
</Database>
