<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Database>
    <EnglishText>
        <!-- Crises Settings -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_MORE_CRISES_NAME">
			<Text>More Crises</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_MORE_CRISES_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>Use alternate and harsher Traditions for the Base Crises.</Text>
		</Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ALTCRISES_NAME">
			<Text>Alternate Crises</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_ALTCRISES_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>Uses Alternate Traditions for the Base Crises.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BASECRISES_NAME">
			<Text>Base Crises</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BASECRISES_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>Unchanged Base Crises.</Text>
		</Row>
        <!-- Antiquity -->
        <!-- Famine Crisis -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_FAMINE_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Antiquity Famine Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_FAMINE_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Food shortages strain your empire, hampering city growth.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A Drier Summer</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A farmer looks on at a field of dead crops. The rains were later and lighter this year. Those living in the great cities of the world's civilizations notice nothing, until food prices start to rise and migrants from neighboring nations appear on their doorstep. Where will these people go and how will they find food now?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Send the masses to the Towns</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Unlock the Empty Storage and Overworked Farmers crisis policies.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001C_NAME">
            <Text>Let them build shanty towns in the Cities</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC001C_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Unlock the City Slum and City Migration crisis policies.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Shrinking Storehouses</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The hungry masses have begun to leave small towns for massive cities, but no relief can be found. The city warehouses are practically empty and what little food merchants are selling comes with a hefty price. Once bright eyes are now sullen and once full bellies are empty.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Hungry Masses</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A young child looks up at the cloudless sky. "Why have the rain gods forsaken us now?" they cry out. A stark contrast is seen across the land, the cities are exploding with people, while small towns are empty and silent. The wealthy have retreated to their castles while the poor bang on walls and wait in lines, clamoring for food.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Rainfall on the Horizon</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Never has rain felt so good. Children laugh in the streets, jumping in puddles, while parents smile on. Few survived this ordeal, and those who did look worse for wear. Yet, there is hope on the horizon. Perhaps the rural migrants and city folk can get along after all.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Antiquity is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_AFC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
        <!-- Succession Crisis -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_SUCCESSION_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Antiquity Succession Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ANTIQUITY_SUCCESSION_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>The death of an heirless ruler causes a diplomatic disaster.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Royal Funeral</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A nation mourns the Emperor's death. But in the dark halls of the palace, court attendents have already begun to scheme. The Emperor died without naming an heir, and the ambitious are desperate to fill the power vacuum. Within the empire several factions begin to prepare a nominee, while our neighbors look on with interest hoping to take advantage of the chaos.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots. Unlock the Royal Banquet City Project. Diplomatic relations worsen.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A Demand Refused</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The chaos and confusion only grow each day without a ruler. Neighboring kings and queens are demanding their kids are coronated as the ruler of our great nation, but each one is refused. Even the greediest of court advisors knows that power is best kept within the nation where they will have more control over the next ruler. With a recent sighting of troops near the border, the search for an acceptable ruler grows more desperate.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Diplomatic relations worsen.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A Nation Divided</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Everyday townsfolk argue in the streets. Who is the legitimate ruler? The Emperor's brother has amassed an army in the North, while the Emperor's wife has gathered the support of the aristocrats in the capital. Both claim to be the true ruler, but our neighbors are refusing to recognize either one. We are divided and isolated.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. Diplomatic relations worsen.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>The One True Ruler</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A sword pulled from a stone. A glowing figure in a lake. Almost by divine intervention the true heir has been found. The young man rallies the generals, the court attendants, and the aristocrats. The Emperor's brother and wife both have no choice but to acknowledge the legitimacy of our new ruler. Now that the empire's internal struggles have been resolved we can focus on rehabilitating our international image, though we probably need a new succession method.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Antiquity is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_ASC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
        <!-- Exploration -->
        <!-- Inflation Crisis -->
        <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_INFLATION_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Exploration Inflation Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_INFLATION_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>An influx of treasure fleet gold leads to ever rising prices.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Rising Prices</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A lady scoffs at the latest market prices. Her weekly food costs have tripled in the last month alone. Similar grumbles can be heard around the city. If we just had more treasure fleets, every citizen could eat like a king!</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Unending Debts</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Royal advisors hide in their chambers as the Queen storms around the castle. How could our great nation be so deep in debt? Print more money! Demand more treasure tributes! She steadies her shaking hands and takes a breath. Perhaps we can take another loan to cover this one?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>You Can't Eat Gold</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The streets are littered with gold, but all anyone wants is a bite to eat. Wealth is meaningless when everyone has it. Is everyone now a King or a Peasant?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Stabilizing Prices</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>Prices have begun to fall, and now hope begins to rise. The world is almost as it was before. Government funds can now be spent on expanding infrastructure and families are able to save for the future. The wealthy are wealthy and the poor are poor. Well, maybe some things need to change ...</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Exploration is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EINC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
        <!-- Isolationism Crisis -->
         <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_ISOLATIONISM_CRISIS_NAME">
            <Text>Exploration Isolationism Crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EXPLORATION_ISOLATIONISM_CRISIS_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Empires begin to turn inwards, leading to a collapse in international trade.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC001A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Shuttered Markets</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC001A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>After centuries of empires clashing against one another, the leading civilizations have decided to turn inward. Ports and markets are forcibly shut down and merchants find once open borders to be strictly closed. Royal advisors scoff, what could they have that we already don't. Our great civilization will continue without our former trade partners. Surely we have enough internal resources to sustain us.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC001B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC001B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. -1 Trade Route Limit, cannot go below zero. Unlock the Town Specialization Internal Trade Town.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC002A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Unsold Wares</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC002A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A merchant returns to the town square, pulling a cart full of unsold goods. Meanwhile, a young woodworker is unable to find the tools they need at market. No new shipments of goods have arrived in months and the townsfolk grow anxious. Where is the greatness we were promised? The benefits to shutting out the world?</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC002B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC002B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+1 Crisis Policy Slot. -1 Trade Route Limit, cannot go below zero.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC003A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>A Breaking Point</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC003A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>A young scholar groans at her desk. By the time she learns the latest laws and regulations, ten more have been added. The number of banned books feels larger than the books that can still be legally read. Religious ceremonies must be performed in secret while black market goods are kept in the shadows. No outside influence is allowed to corrupt our civilization. Citizens begin to wonder if all this censorship is inspiring artists or stifling them.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC003B_NAME">
            <Text>Continue the crisis</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC003B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>+2 Crisis Policy Slots. -1 Trade Route Limit, cannot go below zero.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC004A_STORYTITLE">
            <Text>Forced Reopening</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC004A_COMPLETION">
            <Text>The whole nation is shaken. Huge boats filled with guns pointed at the royal palace. This great humiliation will not stand. With one decree, the era of isolationism is over. Merchants wave goodbye as the first trade ships leave our harbors once again. We were not the first to look outward again, but we will not be the last.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC004B_NAME">
            <Text>The Age of Exploration is ending.</Text>
        </Row>
        <Row Tag="LOC_EISC004B_DESCRIPTION">
            <Text>Who will carry our legacy?</Text>
        </Row>
    </EnglishText>
</Database>
